mobalytics.gg 2019-09-24

# Mobalytics (Gamers Net) Privacy Policy - Mobalytics

Last Updated: **17th of December, 2018**

At Mobalytics, we care about the privacy of your data and are committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you and why, what we do with that information, and how we handle that information.

Specifically, we’ll cover:

All capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meaning set forth in the Terms.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you use our Services, we collect the following types of information.

#### INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE US

##### ACCOUNT INFORMATION

Some information is required to create an account on our Services, such as your name, email, password and in-game name (e.g., summoner name, battle.net id, etc). If you log into Mobalytics with a social networking credential, such as with your Facebook, Google+, Twitch or Steam account, we will ask permission to access basic information from that account, such as your name and email address. You can stop sharing that information with us at any time by removing Mobalytics’ access to that account.

##### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

To help improve your experience or enable certain features of the Services, you may choose to provide us with additional information, like you product and game preferences to personalize your account.

You may also connect with friends on the Services or invite friends who have not yet joined by providing their email addresses, accessing social networking accounts, or using the contact list on your mobile device. We do not store your contact list and delete it after it is used for adding contacts as friends.

If you contact us or participate in a survey, contest, or promotion, we collect the information you submit such as your name, contact information, and message.

##### INFORMATION FROM THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

When you use the Services, we need to collect the data about your game performance, such as latest match details, season stats, etc. from the game publishers APIs. To do this, we use your in-game name that you have provided to us during the registration process.

If you choose to connect your account on our Services to your account on another service, we may receive information from the other service about you including details you have made available via your privacy settings. For example, if you connect to Facebook, Google, Twitch, Steam, and/or Discord, we may receive information like your name, profile picture, age range, language, email address, and friends list. You may also choose to grant us access to your gameplay, exercise or activity data from another service. You can stop sharing the information from the other service with us by removing our access to that other service.

#### INFORMATION WE RECEIVE FROM YOUR USE OF OUR SERVICES

##### LOCATION INFORMATION

When you create an account with us, we get signals about your current location from information such as your IP address or device settings, to securely and reliably set up and maintain your account and to provide our services to you.

##### USAGE INFORMATION

When you access or use our Services, we receive certain usage data. This includes information about your interaction with the Services, for example, when you view or search specific player performance, create or log into your account, or open or interact with a specific Service feature.

We also collect data about the devices and computers you use to access the Services, including IP addresses, browser type, language, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, and cookie information.

### HOW WE USE INFORMATION

We use the information we collect for the following purposes.

#### PROVIDE AND MAINTAIN THE SERVICES

We use the information we collect to deliver the Services (for the performance of the Terms). For example, we need to use your information to calculate your performance and provide you with your Gamer Performance Index (GPI), personalized advice, display your recent activity, and other trends; to enable the community features of the Services; and to give you customer support.

For the Services’ community features, we may use your information to help you find and connect with other users and to allow other users to find and connect with you. For example, your account contact information allows other users to add you as a friend. When another user has your email in their contact list or in their friend network on a connected service, we show that user that you are a user of the Services.

#### IMPROVE, PERSONALIZE, AND DEVELOP THE SERVICES

We use the information we collect to improve and personalize the Services and to develop new ones. For example, we use the information to troubleshoot and protect against errors; perform data analysis and testing; conduct research and surveys; and develop new features and Services.

We also use your information to make inferences and show you more relevant content. Here are some examples:

  * Based on your in-game performance we will personalize advice that you’re getting from the Service.
  * We may personalize quests, challenges and goals for you based on the goals you previously set or achieved and your historical performance data.

#### COMMUNICATE WITH YOU

We use your information when needed to send you Service notifications and respond to you when you contact us. We also use your information to promote new features or products that we think you would be interested in. You can control marketing communications and most Service notifications by using your notification preferences in account settings or via the “Unsubscribe” link in an email.

#### PROMOTE SAFETY AND SECURITY

We use the information we collect to promote the safety and security of the Services, our users, and other parties. For example, we may use the information to authenticate users, facilitate secure payments, protect against fraud and abuse, respond to a legal request or claim, conduct audits, and enforce our terms and policies.

We use cookies and similar technologies for the purposes described above. For more information, please read our [Cookie Privacy Policy](https://mobalytics.gg/cookie/).

For personal data subject to the GDPR, we rely on several legal bases to process the data. These include when you have given your consent, which you may withdraw at any time using your account settings and other tools; when the processing is necessary to perform a contract with you, e.g., the Terms; and our legitimate interests, such as in improving, personalizing, and developing the Services, marketing new features or products that may be of interest, and promoting safety and security as described above.

### HOW INFORMATION IS SHARED

We do not share your personal information except in the limited circumstances described below.

#### WHEN YOU AGREE OR DIRECT US TO SHARE

You may direct us to disclose your information to others, such as when you use our community features like the forums, 7-day leaderboard, and other social tools. For certain information, we provide you with privacy preferences in account settings and other tools to control how your information is visible to other users of the Services. Just remember that if you choose to participate in a challenge, information like your profile photo, posted messages, challenge results, personal statistics, and achievements, is not governed by your privacy preferences and will be visible to all other challenge participants.

You may also authorize us to share your information with others, for example, with a third-party application when you give it access to your account. Remember that their use of your information will be governed by their privacy policies and terms. You can revoke your consent to share with third-party applications using your account settings.

#### FOR EXTERNAL PROCESSING

We transfer information to our corporate affiliates, service providers, and other partners who process it for us, based on our instructions, and in compliance with this policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. These partners provide us with services globally, including for customer support, information technology, payments, marketing, data analysis, research, and surveys.

#### FOR LEGAL REASONS OR TO PREVENT HARM

We may preserve or disclose information about you to comply with a law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; to assert legal rights or defend against legal claims; or to prevent, detect, or investigate illegal activity, fraud, abuse, violations of our terms, or threats to the security of the Services or the physical safety of any person.

Please note: Our policy is to notify you of legal process seeking access to your information, such as search warrants, court orders, or subpoenas, unless we are prohibited by law from doing so. In cases where a court order specifies a non-disclosure period, we provide delayed notice after the expiration of the non-disclosure period. Exceptions to our notice policy include exigent or counterproductive circumstances, for example, when there is an emergency involving a danger of death or serious physical injury to a person.

We may share non-personal information that is aggregated or de-identified so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify an individual. We may disclose such information publicly and to third parties, for example, in public reports about player performance, to partners under agreement with us, or as part of the community benchmarking information we provide to users of our subscription services.

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, purchase or sale of assets, or transition of service to another provider, then your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract.

### YOUR RIGHTS TO ACCESS AND CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We give you account settings and tools to access and control your personal data, as described below, regardless of where you live. If you live in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, and Switzerland (the “Designated Countries”), you have a number of legal rights with respect to your information, which your account settings and tools allow you to exercise, as outlined below subject to applicable law.

#### Accessing and Exporting Data

By logging into your account, you can access much of your personal information. You can request access to a copy (including a “portable” copy) of the personal data that we have collected by sending your request to privacy@mobalyitcs.gg

#### Editing and Deleting Data

Your account settings let you change and delete your personal information. For instance, you can edit or delete the profile data you provide and delete your account if you wish.

If you choose to delete your account, please note that while most of your information will be deleted within 30 days, it may take up to 90 days to delete all of your information, like the data stored in our backup systems. This is due to the size and complexity of the systems we use to store data. We may also preserve data for legal reasons or to prevent harm, including as described in the How Information Is Shared section.

#### Objecting to Data Use

We give you account settings and tools to control our data use. For example, through your privacy settings, you can limit how your information is visible to other users of the Services; using your notification settings, you can limit the notifications you receive from us; and under your application settings, you can revoke the access of third-party applications that you previously connected to your Mobalytics account at any time.

If you live in a Designated Country, in certain circumstances, you can object to our processing of your information based on our legitimate interests, including as described in the How We Use Information section. You have a general right to object to the use of your information for direct marketing purposes. Please see your notification settings to control our marketing communications to you about Mobalytics products. Please also review our [Cookie Privacy Policy](https://mobalytics.gg/cookie/) for your options to control how we and our partners use cookies and similar technologies.

#### Restricting or Limiting Data Use

In addition to the various controls that we offer, if you reside in a Designated Country, you can seek to restrict our processing of your data in certain circumstances. Please note that you can always delete your account at any time.

#### Lodging a Complaint

If you are located in one of the Designated Countries, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you believe our processing of your personal information violates applicable law.

### DATA RETENTION

We keep your account information, like your name, email address, and password, for as long as your account is in existence because we need it to operate your account. In some cases, when you give us information for a feature of the Services, we delete the data after it is no longer needed for the feature. For instance, when you provide your contact list for finding friends on the Services, we delete the list after it is used for adding contacts as friends.

We keep other information, like your performance data that was obtained from game publishers API or calculated with our algorithms as long as necessary for our legitimate business interests.

We also keep information about you and your use of the Services for as long as necessary for our legitimate business interests, for legal reasons, and to prevent harm, including as described in the How We Use Information and How Information Is Shared sections.

### ANALYTICS AND ADVERTISING SERVICES PROVIDED BY OTHERS

We work with partners who provide us with analytics and advertising services. This includes helping us understand how users interact with the Services, serving ads on our behalf across the internet, and measuring the performance of those ads. These companies may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about your interactions with the Services and other websites and applications. To learn more and about your privacy choices, please read our [Cookie Privacy Policy](https://mobalytics.gg/cookie/).

### THIRD PARTY WEBSITES AND APPLICATIONS

The Services may contain links to other websites and applications. In addition, other websites and applications may reference or link to our Services. These websites and applications are not controlled by us. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of each website and application with which they interact. We do not endorse, screen or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites or applications. Visiting these other websites or applications is at your own risk.

### OUR POLICIES FOR CHILDREN

Our Services are not directed to children under 13 (or other age as required by local law), and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under the minimum legal age without parental consent, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible. Parents who believe that their child has submitted personal information to us and would like to have it deleted may contact us at privacy@mobalytics.gg.

### INFORMATION SECURITY

We use a combination of technical, administrative, and physical controls to maintain the security of your information. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.

If you have a security-related concern, please contact Customer Support.

### OUR INTERNATIONAL OPERATIONS AND DATA TRANSFERS

We operate internationally and transfer information to the United States and other countries for the purposes described in this policy. By providing Mobalytics with information, you agree that the transfer, processing and storage of your information globally is necessary for the performance of the Terms. If you do not agree to this, you may delete your Mobalytics account as described in the Your Rights To Access and Control Your Personal Data.

Please note that the countries where we operate may have privacy and data protection laws that differ from, and are potentially less protective than, the laws of your country.

### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion. If there are any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you as required by applicable law. You understand and agree that you will be deemed to have accepted the updated Privacy Policy if you continue to use the Services after the new Privacy Policy takes effect.

### QUESTIONS

If you have questions, suggestions, or concerns about this policy, or about our use of your information, please contact us at [privacy@mobalytics.gg.](mailto:%20privacy@mobalytics.gg)

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept [Read More](https://mobalytics.gg/cookie/)
